Jensen, Vernon Papers /3002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 10th through 16th, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 17th through 23rd, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 24th through 30th, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 1st through 7th, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 8th through 14th, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 15th through 21st, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 22nd through 28th, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 29th through 31st, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Licensing Division Weekly Reports of Operations (June 2, 9, 16, 23, 30), 1961 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 18th through 20th, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 21st through 27th, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 28th through Dec. 4th, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 5th through 11th, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 12th through 18th, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 19th through 25th, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 27th through Jan. 1st, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 2nd through 8th, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 9th through 15th, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 16th through 22nd, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 23rd through 29th, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 30th through 31st, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 1st through 8th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 9th through 15th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 16th through 22nd, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 23rd through 29th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 30th through Nov. 5th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 6th through 12th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 13th through 19th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 20th through 26th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 27th through Dec. 3rd, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 4th through 10th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 11th through 17th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 18th through 24th, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 25th through 31st, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 1st through 2nd, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 3rd through 9th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 10th through 16th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 17th through 23rd, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 24th through 30th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 31st through Aug. 6th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug 7th through 13th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug. 14th through 20th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug. 21st through 27th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug. 28th through Sept. 3rd, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sept. 4th through 10th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sept. 11th through 17th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sept. 18th through 24th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sept. 25th through 30th, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 1st through 8th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 9th through 15th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 16th through 22nd, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 23rd through 29th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 30th through May 6th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 7th through 13th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 14th through 20th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 21st through 27th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 28th through Jun. 3rd, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jun. 4th through 10th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jun. 11th though 17th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jun. 18th through 24th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jun. 25th through 30th, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 1st through 8th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 9th through 15th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 16th through 22nd, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 23rd through 29th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jul. 30th through Aug. 5th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug. 6th through 12th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug. 13th through 19th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug. 20th through 26th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Aug. 27th through Sep. 2nd, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sep. 3rd through 9th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sep. 10th through 16th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sep. 17th through 23rd, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Sep. 24th through 30th, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 1st through 8th, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 9th through 15th, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 16th through 22nd, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 23rd through 28th, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 30th through Dec. 6th, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 7th through 13th, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 14th through 20th, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 21st through 27th, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 28th through Jan. 3rd, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 4th through 10th, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 11th through 17th, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 18th through 24th, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Jan. 25th through 31st, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Feb. 1st through 7th, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Feb. 8th through 14th, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Feb. 15th through 21st, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Feb. 22nd through 28th and 29th, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Mar. 1st through 6th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Mar. 7th through 13th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Mar. 14th through 20th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Mar. 21st through 27th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Mar. 28th through Apr. 3rd, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 4th through 10th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 11th through 17th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 18th through 24th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 25th through May 1st, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 2nd through 8th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 9th through 15th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 16th through 22nd, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 23rd through 29th, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: May 30th through 31st, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- History of NYS Bd. Of Mediation, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Comm. On Research and Publications, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- 1967 Workshop Seminar in Labor Relations and Collective Bargaining for Printing Management (Box 38, Folder 3)
- 1967 Workshop Seminar in Labor Relations and Collective Bargaining for Printing (Box 38, Folder 4)
- National Right to Work Committee, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)